import NWD1 from "./NWD1.mp4" 
import NWD2 from "./NWD2.mp4"
import NWD3 from "./NWD3.mp4"
import NWD4 from "./NWD4.mp4"
import NWD5 from "./NWD5.mp4"
import NWD6 from "./NWD6.mp4"
import NWD7 from "./NWD7.mp4"
import NWD8 from "./NWD8.mp4"
import NWD9 from "./NWD9.mp4"
import NWD10 from "./NWD10.mp4"
import NWD11 from "./NWD11.mp4"
import NWD12 from "./NWD12.mp4"
import NWD13 from "./NWD13.mp4"
import NWD15 from "./NWD15.mp4"
import NWD16 from "./NWD16.mp4"
import NWD17 from "./NWD17.mp4"
import NWD18 from "./NWD18.mp4"
import NWD19 from "./NWD19.mp4"
import NWD20 from "./NWD20.mp4"
import NWD21 from "./NWD21.mp4"
import NWD22 from "./NWD22.mp4"
import NWD24 from "./NWD24.mp4"
import NWD25 from "./NWD25.mp4"
import NWD26 from "./NWD26.mp4"
import NWD27 from "./NWD27.mp4"
import NWD28 from "./NWD28.mp4"
import NWD29 from "./NWD29.mp4"
import NWD31 from "./NWD31.mp4"
import NWD32 from "./NWD32.mp4"
import NWD33 from "./NWD33.mp4"
import NWD34 from "./NWD34.mp4"
import NWD35 from "./NWD35.mp4"
import NWD36 from "./NWD36.mp4"
import NWD37 from "./NWD37.mp4"
import NWD38 from "./NWD38.mp4"
import NWD39 from "./NWD39.mp4"
import NWD40 from "./NWD40.mp4"
import NWD41 from "./NWD41.mp4"

export const NEW11 =[
    {
        id: 419,
        videoFile: NWD41,
        rusQuestion: "использовать,усилие рычага",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to use something that you already have in order to achieve something new or better:",
        answer: "leverage",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 418,
        videoFile: NWD40,
        rusQuestion: "допродажи",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to try to persuade a customer who is already buying something to buy more, or to buy something more expensive:",
        answer: "upsell",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 417,
        videoFile: NWD39,
        rusQuestion: "как показано на канале tv dot com",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the site where to find winning products",
        answer: "as seen on tv dot com",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 416,
        videoFile: NWD38,
        rusQuestion: "открыть ссылку в новой вкладке",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "save the find product for the next overview",
        answer: "open link in a new tab",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 415,
        videoFile: NWD37,
        rusQuestion: "ниша",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "interesting to, aimed at, or affecting only a small number of people:",
        answer: "niche",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 414,
        videoFile: NWD36,
        rusQuestion: "покупка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to buy something:",
        answer: "purchase",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 413,
        videoFile: NWD35,
        rusQuestion: "валюта",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the money that is used in a particular country at a particular time:",
        answer: "currency",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 412,
        videoFile: NWD34,
        rusQuestion: "исследование продукта",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the process of deciding which new products might be successful, and the best way to develop and sell them:",
        answer: "product research",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 411,
        videoFile: NWD33,
        rusQuestion: "всякий раз, когда вам",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "every or any time:",
        answer: "whenever",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 410,
        videoFile: NWD32,
        rusQuestion: "это всегда даст вам ракурс",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a position from which something is looked at:  a way of considering, judging, or dealing with something:",
        answer: "angles",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 409,
        videoFile: NWD31,
        rusQuestion: "насыщенный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "completely filled with something so that no more can be added:",
        answer: "saturated",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 408,
        videoFile: NWD29,
        rusQuestion: "кучу денег",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "infml much or many:",
        answer: "loads of money",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 407,
        videoFile: NWD28,
        rusQuestion: "шесть цифр , шестизначная цифра",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the symbol for a number or an amount expressed in numbers:",
        answer: "six figures",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 406,
        videoFile: NWD27,
        rusQuestion: "трюки",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "something that is not serious or of real value that is used to attract people's attention or interest temporarily, especially to make them buy something:",
        answer: "gimmick",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 405,
        videoFile: NWD26,
        rusQuestion: "тщеславие",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the fact that you are too interested in your appearance or achievements:",
        answer: "vanity",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 404,
        videoFile: NWD25,
        rusQuestion: "удобство",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "suitable for your purposes and needs and causing the least difficulty:",
        answer: "convenience",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 403,
        videoFile: NWD24,
        rusQuestion: "осанка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the way in which someone usually holds their shoulders, neck, and back, or a particular position in which someone stands, sits, etc.:",
        answer: "posture",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 402,
        videoFile: NWD22,
        rusQuestion: "адаптированный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "made or changed especially to be suitable for a particular situation or purpose:",
        answer: "tailored",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 401,
        videoFile: NWD21,
        rusQuestion: "прибыли",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the difference between the total cost of making and selling something and the price it is sold for:",
        answer: "profit margin",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 400,
        videoFile: NWD20,
        rusQuestion: "продвигать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to encourage people to like, buy, use, do, or support something:",
        answer: "promote",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 399,
        videoFile: NWD19,
        rusQuestion: "уход",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the things that you do to make your appearance clean and neat, for example brushing your hair, or the things that you do to keep an animal's hair or fur clean and neat:",
        answer: "grooming",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 398,
        videoFile: NWD18,
        rusQuestion: "широкий",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "very wide:",
        answer: "broad",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 397,
        videoFile: NWD17,
        rusQuestion: "ликвидировать разрыв",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to connect two things or to make the difference between them smaller:",
        answer: "bridge the gap",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 396,
        videoFile: NWD16,
        rusQuestion: "переход",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to move easily and without interruption from one piece of music, part of a story, subject, or situation to another:",
        answer: "segue",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 395,
        videoFile: NWD15,
        rusQuestion: "агент по снабжению",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the act of getting something, especially products or materials, from a particular place:",
        answer: "sourcing agent",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 394,
        videoFile: NWD13,
        rusQuestion: "идеальный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "perfect, or the best possible:",
        answer: "ideal",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 393,
        videoFile: NWD12,
        rusQuestion: "в некотором роде",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to some degree:",
        answer: "somewhat",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 392,
        videoFile: NWD11,
        rusQuestion: "подвижность , ловкость , быстрота",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the ability to move your body quickly and easily:",
        answer: "agility",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 391,
        videoFile: NWD10,
        rusQuestion: "насколько хорошо он будет работать",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "to operate/not operate in a satisfactory way:",
        answer: "perform well",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 390,
        videoFile: NWD9,
        rusQuestion: "оптом",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "in large amounts:",
        answer: "in bulk",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 389,
        videoFile: NWD8,
        rusQuestion: "выполнение заказа",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "the process of taking orders and sending products to customers:",
        answer: "order fulfilment",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 388,
        videoFile: NWD7,
        rusQuestion: "поставщик",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a company, person, etc. that provides things that people want or need, especially over a long period of time:",
        answer: "supplier",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 387,
        videoFile: NWD6,
        rusQuestion: "запускать рекламу",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "run advertising",
        answer: "run ads",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 386,
        videoFile: NWD5,
        rusQuestion: "Основной поток",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "considered normal, and having or using ideas, beliefs, etc. that are accepted by most people:",
        answer: "mainstream",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 385,
        videoFile: NWD4,
        rusQuestion: "соответствующий , уместный",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "connected with what is happening or being discussed:",
        answer: "relevant",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 384,
        videoFile: NWD3,
        rusQuestion: "выбранный вручную",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "used to describe someone who has been carefully chosen for a particular job or activity:",
        answer: "hand picked",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 383,
        videoFile: NWD2,
        rusQuestion: "викторина , контрольный опрос",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "a short, informal test:a game or competition in which you answer questions:",
        answer: "quiz",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
    {
        id: 382,
        videoFile: NWD1,
        rusQuestion: "Прямая поставка",
        before: false,
        border: false,
        engDescription: "an arrangement in which a manufacturer sends products directly to buyers at the request of businesses who advertise and sell the products but do not stock them:",
        answer: "dropshipping",
        myAnswer: "",
        color: "rgb(43, 198, 226)",
        getIdx: 1,
        timeGo: 4000,
        getHight: 1
    },
] 
       